{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"﻿admirali","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"afri","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"aktivisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"aktivisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"alkoholi","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"alkoholi","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"alkoholi","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"alkoholi","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"alkoholi","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"alkoholi","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"alpinisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"alpinisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ameri","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"analiti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"anglisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"anglisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"antialkoholi","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"antialkoholi","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"antialkoholi","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"antialkoholi","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"antialkoholi","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"antialkoholi","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"arhitekti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"arhivisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"arhivisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"automehani","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"automehani","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"automehani","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"automehani","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"automehani","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"automehani","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"autor","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"autori","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"avion","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"babi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"baca","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"baca","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"baca","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"baca","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"baca","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ba","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ba","osnova2":"va","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ba","osnova2":"var","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ba","osnova2":"varev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ba","osnova2":"varica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ba","osnova2":"vari","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ba","osnova2":"varov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ba","osnova2":"varski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ba","osnova2":"vica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"balkon","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"balon","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bani","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"banjolu","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"baruni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bazen","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"be","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"beletristi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"benkova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"beskona","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"beskona","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"beskona","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"biciklisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"biciklisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bilježni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bilježni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bjelogori","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"blizana","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"blizan","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bogataši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bojni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bojni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"boksa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"boksa","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"boksa","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"boksa","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bolni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bra","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bra","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"branitelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"brbljav","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"brbljavi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"br","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"br","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bren","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"brisa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"broja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"broj","osnova2":"anik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bron","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bron","osnova2":"ani","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bubnjari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bu","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bu","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bu","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"budali","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bukovi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"busova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"cari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ci","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"cimeri","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"cin","osnova2":"ani","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"cjev","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"crikveni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"crnogori","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"crtan","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"crti","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"curi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"cvjeta","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"cvr","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"cvr","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"adski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"akove","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"amac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"apljinski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arapa","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aroban","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arobnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arobni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arobnja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arobnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arobnjakov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"as","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"asnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"asni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"asni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"asnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"asnikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"asopis","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aša","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avao","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"egrtaljka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekanje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekaona","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekaonica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekrk","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"elik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"elo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"empres","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"est","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"esti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estit","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estitati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estitka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estito","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estitost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"esto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estoća-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešalj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"eški","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešljanje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešljaona","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešljaonica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešljati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etiri","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etiristo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etiristoti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etkati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etkica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdeset","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdesetak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdesetero","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdeseti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdesetogodišnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdesetogodišnjakinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdesetogodišnji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdesetogodišnjica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdesetorica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrnaest","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrnaestero","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrnaesti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etveri","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvero","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverodijelan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverodimenzijski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverodimenzionalni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverogodišnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverogodišnjakinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverogodišnji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverokatni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverokatnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverokratnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverokut","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etveromjese","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etveroredan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverorje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverosjed","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverosoban","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverostruk","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvorica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvorka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrt","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtaš","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtašica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtinka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"eznuti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"igra","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ijigod","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ikaški","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ileanski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"im","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"im","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"imbenik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"inele","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"initi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"initi se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"injenica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ip","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ist","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ista","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ista","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ista","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ista","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ista","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"istiona","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"istionica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"istiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ita","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itanka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itaona","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itaonica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itav","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itlu","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"izma","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"lan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"lanak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"lanica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"lani","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"lanov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"lanski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"okolada","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ovjek","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uditi se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"udo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uvati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"vor","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"vor","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"vrst","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"vrsto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ćelav","osnova2":"ev-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ćevap","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ćirili","osnova2":"ni-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dalekopisa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"daltonisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"daš","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"de","osnova2":"ko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"de","osnova2":"kov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"delni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"desetni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"desetni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"desetomjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dešnja","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"devetomjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"di","osnova2":"iti se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dijeteti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dinami","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"direktori","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dizajneri","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"akov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"ji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"djevi","osnova2":"anski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"djevi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"djevoja","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"djevoj","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"djevoj","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"djevoj","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dla","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"asnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"asni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"asni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"asnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"asnikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"im","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"doktori","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"domaći","osnova2":"in-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"donjomiholja","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"doru","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"doru","osnova2":"kovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dra","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"druga","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"drugaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"druk","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dubrova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dudaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"duga","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dugooto","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"duši","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dvojezi","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dvoli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dvoli","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dvoli","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dvomjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dvorje","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dvoto","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"đakova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"đavol","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"đavol","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"đavol","osnova2":"ićev-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"đavoli","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"đurđeva","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"egzoti","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"fagotisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"fagotisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"fizi","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"fizi","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"flautisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"flautisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"frulaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gajdaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"garešni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"generali","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gimnasti","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gimnasti","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gimnasti","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gimnasti","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gimnasti","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gimnasti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gitaristi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gitaristi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gla","osnova2":"alo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gla","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"glagolji","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gledatelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gležnja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gluma","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"glum","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"glumi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gra","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"grada","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gradona","osnova2":"elnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gramati","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gr","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"grija","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"guš","osnova2":"etina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"guš","osnova2":"ji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"harfisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"harfisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"harmonikaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"hercegova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"hla","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"hr","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"hrvata","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"hu","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"hu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"humoristi","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"i","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"idealisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"idealisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ilo","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"iluzionisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"imeni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ina","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"informati","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"informati","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"informati","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"informati","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"informati","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ira","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"iseljeni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"isklju","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"isklju","osnova2":"ivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ispri","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ispri","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ispri","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"isto","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ivan","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ivane","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"izborni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"izdaji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"izdajni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"izdajni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ja","osnova2":"anje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ja","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ja","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jaja","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jamaja","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"janjeva","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jastu","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"javnobilježni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"je","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jedini","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jedna","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jednojezi","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jednomjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jednorje","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jezi","osnova2":"ac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jezi","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jezi","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jezi","osnova2":"av","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jezi","osnova2":"avost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jezi","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ju","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ju","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jugoisto","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"juna","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"južnoafri","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"južnoameri","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kalja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kapetani","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kapulja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"karlova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"katoli","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kau","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kembri","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kipari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kiselja","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"klarinetisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"klarinetisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"klaviristi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"klaviristi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kle","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"klju","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"književni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"arstvo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ko","osnova2":"ijaš","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ko","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kola","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"koli","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"koli","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"komandanti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kona","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kona","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kona","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"konobari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kontrabasisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kontrabasisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kopa","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"koprivni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kor","osnova2":"ulanski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"korisni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"korisni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kornja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kota","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kova","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kov","osnova2":"eg","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kovr","osnova2":"av","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kovr","osnova2":"avost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kozmeti","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kozmeti","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kozmeti","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kozmeti","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kozmeti","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kozmeti","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kozmeti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kr","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kr","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"križeva","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"krma","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kroja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kroja","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kroja","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kroja","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kroja","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ksilofonisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kućani","osnova2":"in-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kuhari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kum","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kupaoni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kup","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kvadrati","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ladi","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lan","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"latini","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lavi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"li","osnova2":"inka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"li","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"nikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lijeri","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lijeri","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lijeri","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lijeri","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lijeri","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lingvisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lingvisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lisi","osnova2":"ji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lon","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lopo","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lov","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ljekarni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ljekarni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ljubi","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ljubim","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ljubimi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ljulja","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"kica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mađioni","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mađioni","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mađioni","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mađioni","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mađioni","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mađioni","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"maj","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"maj","osnova2":"inski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"majori","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mandolinisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mandolinisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"marijabistri","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"masla","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"matemati","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"matemati","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"matemati","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"matemati","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"matemati","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"matemati","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"materijalisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"materijalisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"maturanti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mehani","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mehani","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mehani","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mehani","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mehani","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mehani","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"meksi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"menadžeri","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mesari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"minira","osnova2":"unalo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ministri","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"minobaca","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mjenja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mjenja","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mjenja","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mjenja","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mjese","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mjese","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mladun","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mlije","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"moma","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mom","osnova2":"ad","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mornari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mornari","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mozambi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"muškar","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"na","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nadnaredni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nadnaredni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nanora","osnova2":"unalo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nao","osnova2":"ale","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naran","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naran","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naredni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naredni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naslonja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nastavni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nastavni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naši","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"natika","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"natjecatelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"natje","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"natporu","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"natporu","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"natporu","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"natporu","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"natporu","osnova2":"nikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nau","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nave","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"navija","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"navija","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"navija","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"navija","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"navija","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"neodlu","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"neodlu","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"neodlu","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepliva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepliva","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepliva","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepliva","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepuša","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepuša","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepuša","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepuša","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepuša","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nevodi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nevoza","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nevoza","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nevoza","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nevoza","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nevoza","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ni","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nogometaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nosa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nov","osnova2":"anica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nov","osnova2":"anik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"novorođen","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"njema","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obi","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obi","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"iti se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obljetni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"oboisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"oboisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obrtni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obrtni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"ekivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"inski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"it","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"ito","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"uh","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"uhov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odašilja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odbojkaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odgojitelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odli","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ogrta","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"okulisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"opkora","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"optimisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"orguljaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"osigura","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"osmomjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"otklju","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"otklju","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"oto","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"otvara","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ozna","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ozna","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pacijenti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pa","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pa","osnova2":"etina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pa","osnova2":"ji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pakra","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pala","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pala","osnova2":"inka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pal","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"papu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"partneri","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pastiri","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pau","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pau","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"ela","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pedagogi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pekari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pesimisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"petomjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pijanisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pijanisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pisa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"piš","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pjesni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pješa","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pješ","osnova2":"anik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pjeva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pjeva","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pjeva","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pjeva","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pjeva","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"ljiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"ljivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"ljivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plamenja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plesa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plesa","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plesa","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plesa","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plesa","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pliva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pliva","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pliva","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pliva","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pliva","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plo","osnova2":"anski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plo","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plja","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pljuva","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"ešljati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"etak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"eti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"etnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"injati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"podru","osnova2":"je","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"podru","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poja","osnova2":"alo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pokaziva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pokriva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"policaj","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"polusloženi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"polji","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poljoprivredni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poljoprivredni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pore","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poru","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poru","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poru","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poru","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poru","osnova2":"nikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poštari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"potporu","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"potporu","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"potporu","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"potporu","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"potporu","osnova2":"nikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"potpukovni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"potpukovni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poznani","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pozorni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pozorni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"anjski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"predsjedni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"predsjedni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"predstavni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"predstavni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prekida","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"presko","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prevoditelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"anje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"est","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prigušiva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prijatelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"priklju","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"priklju","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pripovjeda","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pripovjeda","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pripovjeda","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pripovjeda","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pristupa","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pristupa","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pristupa","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"privla","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"privla","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"privla","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"elje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"išćiva","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"itati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prodava","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prodava","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prodava","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prodava","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prodava","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"profesori","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"proizvođa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"proizvođa","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"proizvođa","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prolazni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prolazni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prometni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prometni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prora","osnova2":"un","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prosje","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prosje","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prosje","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prostira","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"protivni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"protivni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prou","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prou","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prva","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prvaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pti","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pu","osnova2":"iški","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pukovni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pukovni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"punja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"puša","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"puša","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"puša","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"puša","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"puša","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"putni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"putni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"ji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"un","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"unalni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"unalo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"unalstvo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"unati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"radni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"radni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"raj","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ranjeni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ranjeni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rasplinja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"raspršiva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"raš","osnova2":"lamba","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ratni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ratni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ravnatelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"razli","osnova2":"it","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"razli","osnova2":"ito","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"razli","osnova2":"itost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"razvodni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"razvodni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"re","osnova2":"enica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"redovni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"redovni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ribari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rije","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rije","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rije","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rimokatoli","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rje","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"nikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"roditelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rođa","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rombi","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ronila","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ronio","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ronitelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rukometaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rup","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ruži","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ruži","osnova2":"asto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"saksofonisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"saksofonisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"satni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"satni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"savija","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sebi","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sebi","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sebi","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sedmomjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"selja","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sendvi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sestri","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sestri","osnova2":"nin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sije","osnova2":"anj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"simpati","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"simpati","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sisa","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sjeveroisto","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"skijaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"skladatelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sko","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"skupni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slasti","osnova2":"arna","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slasti","osnova2":"arnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slatkorje","osnova2":"iv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slatkorje","osnova2":"ivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slatkorje","osnova2":"ivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sli","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sli","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slikari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slu","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slu","osnova2":"ajan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slu","osnova2":"ajno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slu","osnova2":"ajnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"smo","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sobari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"so","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"so","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"so","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sopilaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"spi","osnova2":"anski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"spisatelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sportaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sprema","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sprema","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sprema","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sprema","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sprema","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"srda","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"srda","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"srda","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stan","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stanovni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stara","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"star","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stepeni","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"arica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"ari","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"arstvo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stomatologi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"strana","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stran","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stri","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"strijel","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stru","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stru","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stru","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stru","osnova2":"njak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stru","osnova2":"njakinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"strunja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"studenti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"suboti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"su","osnova2":"elje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"suda","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sud","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sudioni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sun","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sun","osnova2":"ano","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sun","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sure","osnova2":"enica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"suvoza","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"suvoza","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"suvoza","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"suvoza","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"suvoza","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sva","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sve","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sve","osnova2":"ano","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sve","osnova2":"anost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sveta","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"svet","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sveti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sveu","osnova2":"ilište","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"svira","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"svira","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"svira","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"svira","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"šahisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"šestomjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"šumari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tajni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tajni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"taksisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tamburaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"te","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tehni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tenisa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tenisa","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tenisa","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tenisa","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tenisa","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"timpanisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"to","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"to","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"to","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"to","osnova2":"kica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"to","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"to","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tra","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tratin","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"travni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tr","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"trećaši","osnova2":"in-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"treneri","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"trenuta","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"trenuta","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"trgova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"trgov","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"trombonisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tromjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"trorje","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"troto","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"truba","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"truba","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"truba","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"truba","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"truba","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tubisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"njava","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"turisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"turisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":".","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"enica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"eni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"eni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"enik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"enikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"estalost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"initi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iona","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"ionica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"itelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iteljev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iteljica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"itelji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iteljski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"uklju","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"uklju","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"umirovljeni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"umjetni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"unato","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"uo","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"upalja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"upravlja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"uređiva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"usisava","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"uskli","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"uskli","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"uspinja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vadi","osnova2":"ep","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"valpova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"valj","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vari","osnova2":"ela","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vaterpolisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vaterpolisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vatrogaš","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"era","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"eras","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"erati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"ernji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vegetarijan","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vele","osnova2":"asni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"veli","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"velikogori","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"velolu","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"velja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vesla","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vesla","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vesla","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vesla","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vesla","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vezni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"viceadmirali","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vinkova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violinisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violinisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elist","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elistica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elisti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elisti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elistov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"viroviti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"višejezi","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"višekratni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"višemjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vje","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjen","osnova2":"anje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjen","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjerni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjerou","osnova2":"itelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjerou","osnova2":"iteljev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjerou","osnova2":"iteljica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjerou","osnova2":"itelji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjerou","osnova2":"iteljski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vježbeni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vježbeni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vladari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vlasni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vodenja","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vodi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vodi","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vodi","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vodi","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vodi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vodni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vodni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vojni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"voza","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"voza","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"voza","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"voza","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"voza","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vraži","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vu","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zagreba","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zaje","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zajedni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zaklju","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zaklju","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zamjeni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zamjeni","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zamrziva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zapo","osnova2":"eti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zavi","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ze","osnova2":"etina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ze","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ze","osnova2":"ji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zidari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zlo","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zna","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zna","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"znan","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"znani","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zuba","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zubari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zvjezda","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zvr","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ži","osnova2":"ara","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"žli","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"žumbera","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"župani","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
